Guide to the Francis J. McNamara papers, 1928-1997
George Mason University Libraries
- Series 1: Anti-Communism and Subversive Activities, 1928-1975; (154 boxes)
  - Wiretapping - Notes - misc., 1974-1976 (Folder 19, Box 151)
    National Commission for the Review of Federal and State Laws
  - Wiretapping - Business Week - article "An end to free phone information", June 22, 1974 (Folder 20, Box 151)
    Cincinnati Bell
  - Wiretapping - "What's Next, Professor Bell?" Bell Industries Article, ca. 1976 (Folder 1, Box 152)
    Alexander Graham Bell, History of Telephone
  - Wiretapping - Human Events - "Rusk Has Bad Memory on Pre-Watergate Wiretapping', June 29, 1974 (Folder 2, Box 152)
    Rusk, Wiretapping, Watergate
  - Wiretapping - CWA Convention Resolution 36A-74-7 "Service Monitoring" As Adopted (3 copies), 1974 (Folder 3, Box 152)
  - Wiretapping - Playboy Articles - "Big Brother in America", January 1967 (Folder 4, Box 152)
  - Wiretapping - Subversive Activities Control Board, February 15, 1968 (Folder 5, Box 152)
  - Wiretapping - Electro Debugger Brochure, ca. 1970s (Folder 6, Box 152)
    Mail-Order Form
  - Wiretapping - Department of Justice - statement of Henry E. Peterson, 1974 (Folder 7, Box 152)
    Department of Justice, Electronic Surveillance, Wiretapping
  - Wiretapping - Survey Results - Recent Harris Poll, 1968 (Folder 8, Box 152)
    Poll Directions
  - Wiretapping - Sid Goldberg, March 16, 1974 (Folder 9, Box 152)
    Goldberg, Nixon, State Department, Watergate
  - Wiretapping - Envelope Photocopies: Communications Workers of America - Don Evans, 1974 (Folder 10, Box 152)
    Envelope Photocopies
  - Wiretapping - The National Wiretap Commission, 1975 (Folder 11, Box 152)
    Electronic Surveillance, Wiretapping
  - Wiretapping - Availability of information from Federal Departments and Agencies, 1961 (Folder 12, Box 152)
    Committee on Government Operations
  - Wiretapping - Warrantless Wiretapping and Electronic Surveillance, 1975 (Folder 13, Box 152)
    Committee on Foreign Relations, Committee on the Judiciary
  - Wiretapping - Office of the Attorney General - Washington D.C., 1972 (Folder 14, Box 152)
    Correspondence, Department of Justice
  - Wiretapping - Office of the Attorney General - Washington D.C., 1967 (Folder 15, Box 152)
    Correspondence, Department of Justice, Subversive Activities Control Board
  - Wiretapping - Dept. of Justice - Statement of Henry Peterson, with Post Article, April 27, 1974 (Folder 16, Box 152)
    Department of Justice, Electronic Surveillance, Peterson
  - Wiretapping and Eavesdropping - summary - report of hearings 1958 - 1961, 1962 (Folder 17, Box 152)
    Committee on the Judiciary
  - Wiretapping - Statement by Senator Charles McC. Mathias, JR at a hearing on Warrantless Wiretapping and National Security, October 2, 1974 (Folder 18, Box 152)
    National Security, Wiretapping
  - Wiretapping - Statement of Professor B. James George, Council Member - American Bar Association Section of Criminal Justice, October 2, 1974 (Folder 19, Box 152)
    American Bar Association, Committee on the Judiciary
  - Wiretapping - Prepared Statement of William K. Lambie, JR., October 2, 1974 (Folder 20, Box 152)
    Americans for Effective Law Enforcement
  - Wiretapping - Public Law 90-351 - 90th Congress, H.R. 5037, June 19, 1968 (Folder 21, Box 152)
    Omnibus Crime Control, Safe States Act of 1968
  - Wiretapping - Statement of Honorable - Elliot L. Richardson, April 3, 1974 (Folder 22, Box 152)
    Constitutional Rights, Electronic Surveillance, Wiretapping
  - Wiretapping - Time Magazine - article on wiretapping, July 25, 1969 (Folder 23, Box 152)
    Government, Wiretapping
  - Wiretapping - FCC Monitoring of Employees' Telephones, 1973 (Folder 24, Box 152)
  - Wiretapping - FCC Monitoring of Employees' Telephones, 1972 (Folder 25, Box 152)
  - Wiretapping - Informal Opening Remarks - Dean Rusk, May 9, 1974 (Folder 26, Box 152)
  - Wiretapping - Federal Supplement on Wiretapping, July 20, 1973 (Folder 27, Box 152)
  - Wiretapping - U.S District Court - Northern District of Illinois - cause, 1970 (Folder 28, Box 152)
  - Wiretapping Law - Electronic surveillance law, 1972 (Folder 29, Box 152)
  - Wiretapping - Civil Liberties Repression: Fact or Fiction? U.S News and World Report, November 8, 1971 (Folder 30, Box 152)
    Civil Rights, Electronic Surveillance, Wiretapping
  - Wiretapping - The Challenge of Crime of Free Society, February 1967 (Folder 31, Box 152)
    President's Commission on Law Enforcement and Administration of Justice
  - Wiretapping - "Mathias Urges Law to share up constitutional privacy guarantees" News From Senator Charles McMathias, 1974 (Folder 32, Box 152)
    Electronic Surveillance, Privacy Rights
  - Wiretapping - U.S Supreme Court Report - Edward H. Coolridge JR., 1971 (Folder 33, Box 152)
    Electronic Surveillance, Supreme Court
  - Wiretapping - Nomination of Henry A. Kissinger, 1973 (Folder 34, Box 152)
    Committee on Foreign Relations, Kissinger, Secretary of State
  - Wiretapping - Nomination of Henry A. Kissanger, 1973 (Folder 35, Box 152)
  - Wiretapping - Warrantless Wiretapping and electronic surveillance, 1974 (Folder 36, Box 152)
  - Wiretapping - Warrantless Wiretapping - Hearings, June 29, 1972 (Folder 37, Box 152)
    Committee on the Judiciary, Electronic Surveillance, Wiretapping
  - Wiretapping and Electronic Surveillance, 1974 (Folder 1, Box 153)
  - Wiretapping - Dr.Kissinger's Role in Wiretapping - Hearings, September 29, 1974 (Folder 2, Box 153)
    Committee on the Judiciary, Electronic Surveillance, Kissinger, Wiretapping
  - Wiretapping - Omnibus Crime Control and Safe Streets Act of 1967 (Folder 3, Box 153)
    Committee on the Judiciary, McClellan
  - World Government and American Freedom, 1950-1952 (Folder 4, Box 153)
    Transcript of Sermon, World Government
  - World government and world court, 1950 (Folder 5, Box 153)
    World Government
  - World Marxist Review, October-December 1962 (Folder 6, Box 153)
    Anti-Communism, Cold War
  - World Strength of the Communist Party Organizations - 17th Annual Report, January 1965 (Folder 7, Box 153)
  - World Strength of the Communist Party Organizations - 18th Annual Report, January 1966 (Folder 8, Box 153)
  - World Strength of the Communist Party Organizations - 19th Annual Report, 1967 (Folder 9, Box 153)
  - World Strength of the Communist Party Organizations - 20th Annual Report, 1968 (Folder 10, Box 153)
  - WUO, 1971-1981 (Folder 1, Box 154)
    Weather Underground Organization
  - WUO, 1969-1981 (Folder 2, Box 154)
  - Young Socialist Alliance, 1969 (Folder 3, Box 154)
    Socialism, Youth Movements
  - Youth Feast for Freedom Committee, 1969 (Folder 4, Box 154)
    Youth Movements
  - Youth Workers Liberation League, 1970-1973 (Folder 5, Box 154)
  - Youth Workers Liberation League, 1970-1973 (Folder 6, Box 154)
- Series 2: National Security, 1976-1997; (60 boxes)
  The second series covers the second half of Francis McNamara's career, corresponding roughly with the dates 1976-1997. This series contains material from McNamara's career at the Hale Foundation and later work. This series is arranged alphabetically by folder title.
  - Abscam Investigation, 1982 (Folder 1, Box 155)
    Abscam, FBI
  - Abscam Stings, 1980 (Folder 2, Box 155)
  - Abscam Stings, 1980-1983 (Folder 3, Box 155)
    Abscam
  - ACLU, 1986-1993 (Folder 4, Box 155)
    American Civil Liberties Union
  - ACLU-FBI, 1977 (Folder 5, Box 155)
    American Civil Liberties Union, FBI
  - ACLU-[Elizabeth Gurley] Flynn and total [restoration], 1976 (Folder 6, Box 155)
  - Active Measures-El Salvador, 1980s (Folder 7, Box 155)
    Latin America, Grenada, Caribbean
  - Advisory Commission on Public Diplomacy, 1989 (Folder 8, Box 155)
    Reports
  - Aeroflot (Soviet Airlines), 1981-1986 (Folder 9, Box 155)
    Cold War, Espionage
  - Agee, [Philip], Australia script, 1977 (Folder 10, Box 155)
    Agee, Phillip, CIA
  - Agee, [Philip]-passport [revoked] and FOIA, 1979-1981 (Folder 11, Box 155)
    Agee, Phillip, Freedom of Information Act, Passport Case
  - Agee [Philip]-white paper, 1979-1981 (Folder 12, Box 155)
    Agee, Phillip, El Salvador
  - Agee, [Philip]-[Louis] Wolf W.P. [Washington Post] letter, 1981 (Folder 13, Box 155)
    Correspondence
  - Lauro, Achille, 1985 (Folder 14, Box 155)
    PLO, Mohammed Abbas, Hijacking, Terrorism
  - AIDS tests, 1987-1989 (Folder 15, Box 155)
  - Alaska pipeline-off-shore oil rigs [security], 1976-1994 (Folder 16, Box 155)
    Oil Security, Sabotage
  - American Cause, 1976 (Folder 1, Box 156)
    American Cause, United States Sovereignty
  - Ames, Aldrich, 1994-1995 (Folder 2, Box 156)
    America, CIA, Espionage, Soviet Spy, Traitor
  - Ames, Aldrich, 1994-1995 (Folder 3, Box 156)
    American, CIA, Espionage, Soviet Spy, Traitor
  - Alpirez, [Julio Roberto]-[Efrain] Bamaca Velasquez, 1995 (Folder 4, Box 156)
    CIA, Guatemala, Guerrillas
  - [American Sentinel], 1982 (Folder 5, Box 156)
    Defense, Foreign Affairs, National Security
  - [American Sentinel], 1983 (Folder 6, Box 156)
  - [American Sentinel], 1985 (Folder 7, Box 156)
  - [American Sentinel], 1987 (Folder 8, Box 156)
  - [American Sentinel], 1988 (Folder 9, Box 156)
  - [American Sentinel] [indexes], 1989 (Folder 1, Box 157)
  - [American Sentinel: miscellaneous], 1982-1984 (Folder 2, Box 157)
  - Carter, Amy, 1987 (Folder 3, Box 157)
    CIA, Protests
  - ANC African National Congress, 1986-1992 (Folder 4, Box 157)
    Mandela, Nelson, Protests
  - Angola, 1976 (Folder 5, Box 157)
    Cuba, Soviet Intervention, mercenary, Daniel Gearheart
  - Blunt, Anthony, 1979 (Folder 6, Box 157)
    British, Espionage, Soviet Spy
  - [Arlington House Publishers], 1977-1980 (Folder 7, Box 157)
    Correspondence, Notes
  - ARU (Armed Resistance Unit) - Capitol bombing, 1983-1984 (Folder 8, Box 157)
  - ASC, SDI, 'Star Wars' (misc.), 1983-1985 (Folder 9, Box 157)
    American Security Council, Reagan, Strategic Defense Initiative,
  - ASC, SDI, 'Star Wars' (misc.), 1983-1989 (Folder 10, Box 157)
    American Security Council, Reagan, Strategic Defense Initiative
  - ASC, SDI, 'Star Wars' (misc.), 1983-1989 (Folder 11, Box 157)
  - Asner, Edward, 1980-1990 (Folder 1, Box 158)
  - Assassination attempt - Reagan, Ronald [1 of 2], 1981-1982 (Folder 2, Box 158)
    Assassination, John W. Hinckley Jr., Reagan, Ronald
  - Assassination attempt - Reagan, Ronald [2 of 2], 1981-1982 (Folder 3, Box 158)
    Assassination, John W. Hinckley, Washington Hilton, Reagan, Ronald
  - Association of Former Intelligence Officers, 1976-1987 (Folder 4, Box 158)
    AFIO
  - Association of Former Intelligence Officers, 1976-1987 (Folder 5, Box 158)
  - Assassination (genocide) - Rwanda, Burundi, 1994 (Folder 6, Box 158)
    Rwandan Genocide, Rwanda
  - Association of National Security Alumni, 1987-1990 (Folder 7, Box 158)
    CIA
  - A Team-B Team, 1977-1978 (Folder 8, Box 158)
    Congressional Records, Newspaper Clippings
  - Atrocities-crimes, 1980-1990 (Folder 9, Box 158)
    El Salvador
  - Atrocities-crimes, 1980-1990 (Folder 1, Box 159)
  - Baldwin, Roger, 1976-1977 (Folder 2, Box 159)
    USSR
  - Barnett, David H. (CIA-ESP), 1980-1981 (Folder 3, Box 159)
    Christopher John Boyce, Espionage
  - Bauman [Robert E.]-[Jon?] Hinson, 1980-1986 (Folder 4, Box 159)
  - Beirut-U.S. Embassy, Marine compound, 1983-1986 (Folder 5, Box 159)
    DOD Report, House Report, Bombing, Hezbullah, Terrorism
  - Beirut-U.S. Embassy, Marine compound, 1983-1986 (Folder 6, Box 159)
  - Bell, William Holden, 1981-1982 (Folder 7, Box 159)
    Espionage, FBI
  - Bicentennial [U.S.], 1976 (Folder 8, Box 159)
    House Report, Heritage Foundation Report, Debate
  - Bicentennial [U.S.], 1976 (Folder 9, Box 159)
  - Billy Carter, 1980 (Folder 10, Box 159)
    Libya
  - Billy Carter, 1980 (Folder 11, Box 159)
  - Bloch, Felix, 1990-1993 (Folder 1, Box 160)
    FBI, Espionage
  - Bloch, Felix, 1989 (Folder 2, Box 160)
  - Bly, Herman O., 1977-1979 (Folder 3, Box 160)
    Carter, Communism, Religion
  - Brink's, 1983 (Folder 4, Box 160)
    FBI, Bank Robbery, Terrorism
  - Brink's - Boudin, Kathy, 1982-1984 (Folder 5, Box 160)
    Bank Robbery, Terrorism, FBI
  - Boyce [Christopher John]-Lee [Andrew D.], 1977-1985 (Folder 6, Box 160)
  - The Brethren [book title], 1979 (Folder 7, Box 160)
    Supreme Court, William Brennan, Warren E. Burger, Bob Woodward, Scott Armstrong
  - Brink's-federal prosecution, 1981-1988 (Folder 8, Box 160)
    Bank Robbery
  - Bush, George H. W. - Assassination attempt, 1993 (Folder 9, Box 160)
    Assassination, Iraq, Kuwait
  - Bush, George H. W. - Assassination attempts, 1984-1993 (Folder 10, Box 160)
    Iraq, Kuwait
  - CAIB-General [Counter-Watch/Covert Action Information Bulletin], 1977-1981 (Folder 11, Box 160)
    Philip Agee, Havana, Espionage
  - CAIB-General [Counter-Watch/Covert Action Information Bulletin], 1977-1981 (Folder 12, Box 160)
  - Campaign to Stop Government Spying, 1977-1979 (Folder 13, Box 160)
    Espionage, Intelligence
  - Campaign to Stop Government Spying, 1977-1979 (Folder 14, Box 160)
  - Campaign [for Political Rights] news, 1978-1982 (Folder 1, Box 161)
    Materials List
  - Campaign [for Political Rights] news, 1978-1982 (Folder 2, Box 161)
    Campaign Flyers, Notes
  - Carlucci, Frank, 1977-1987 (Folder 3, Box 161)
  - Carmichael, Stokely, 1967-1984 (Folder 4, Box 161)
    Protests
  - Carns, Michael P.C. and John M. Deutch, 1995 (Folder 5, Box 161)
  - Carter Administration, 1976-1982 (Folder 6, Box 161)
  - Carter Administration, 1976-1982 (Folder 7, Box 161)
    Department of Justice, Newspaper Clippings
  - Carter Administration, 1976-1982 (Folder 8, Box 161)
  - "Carter Administration Appointments", ca. 1976 (Folder 9, Box 161)
    Political Appointments, President Carter
  - Carter-Mondale, 1976-1990 (Folder 10, Box 161)
    Mondale, Walter
  - Carter-Mondale, 1976-1990 (Folder 11, Box 161)
  - Carter [James Earl] EO 12036, 1977-1980 (Folder 1, Box 162)
    Carter
  - Carter [James Earl] EO12036, 1978 (Folder 2, Box 162)
    Executive Order, Intelligence
  - Catholic Bishops, 1982-1984 (Folder 3, Box 162)
    Catholic Church
  - Cavanagh, Thomas Patrick, 1984-1985 (Folder 4, Box 162)
  - Chin, Larry Wu-Tai, 1980s (Folder 5, Box 162)
    China, Espionage
  - China, 1979-1988 (Folder 6, Box 162)
  - Christic Institute (lawsuit), 1980-1991 (Folder 7, Box 162)
  - "Churchill and Us" - Edward N. Luttwak, 1977 (Folder 8, Box 162)
    Churchill, Winston
  - CIA-[Philip] Agee (general)-[Steve] Weissman, [Mark] Hosenball, 1976-1991 (Folder 9, Box 162)
    Central Intelligence Agency, Generals
  - CIA agent "massacre", 1977-1978 (Folder 10, Box 162)
    Stansfield Turner, Central Intelligence Agency
  - CIA-[Robert F.] Bodroghy, 1980-1984 (Folder 11, Box 162)
    Central Intelligence Agency, Scandal
  - CIA-budget-personnel, 1978-1983 (Folder 12, Box 162)
    Senate Reports, House Reports, Central Intelligence Agency
  - CIA-budget-personnel, 1982-1984 (Folder 13, Box 162)
    Congressional Record, Central Intelligence Agency
  - CIA-budget-personnel, 1979-1982 (Folder 14, Box 162)
  - CIA-campus exposure and [law] suits (fola), 1976-1982 (Folder 1, Box 163)
    Central Intelligence Agency, Colleges
  - CI [Counter Intelligence] DEF [Definition], 1976-1983 (Folder 2, Box 163)
    Congressional Records, Counterintelligence, Notes
  - CIA-covert operations, 1981-1982 (Folder 3, Box 163)
  - CIA-covert operations, 1976-1982 (Folder 4, Box 163)
  - CIA-covert operations, 1976-1982 (Folder 5, Box 163)
  - CIA-covert operations - Dissertation - Perry, David, 1981-1982 (Folder 6, Box 163)
    Dissertation Draft "Covert Action: An Ethical Analysis" Perry, David
  - CIA - Killings, 1993 (Folder 7, Box 163)
    Pakistan, Fairfax, Mir Aimal Kansi, Central Intelligence Agency, Terrorism
  - CIA-damage general, 1978-1981 (Folder 8, Box 163)
  - CIA FOIA - H.R. 516-9/19/84 - S. 1324-11/17/83 (Folder 9, Box 163)
    Freedom of Information Act, National Security, Central Intelligence Agency
  - CIA-FOIA, 1977-1981 (Folder 10, Box 163)
  - CIA-FOIA, 1977-1981 (Folder 11, Box 163)
  - CIA-general information, 1980-1985 (Folder 1, Box 164)
  - CIA guerrilla manual 1984 (Folder 2, Box 164)
    Central Intelligence Agency, Latin America
  - CIA-[King] Hussein [of Jordan] Washington Post leak, 1977 (Folder 3, Box 164)
    Hussein, Saddam, Jordan, Central Intelligence Agency
  - CIA-Iran (ISA) Demonstration, 1978 (Folder 4, Box 164)
    Central Intelligence Agency, Iran
  - CIA-Moore [Edwin G.] espionage case, 1976-1977 (Folder 5, Box 164)
    Spy, Central Intelligence Agency
  - CIA-Pike committee-[Daniel] Schorr leak-ethics committee, 1976-1980 (Folder 6, Box 164)
  - CIA-reorganization-Ford-EO 11905, 1976 (Folder 7, Box 164)
  - CIA-the Warren Commission, 1976-1977 (Folder 8, Box 164)
  - CISPES (HALE material), 1980s (Folder 9, Box 164)
    El Salvador, FBI
  - Citizens' Legal Defense Fund for the FBI, 1977-1979 (Folder 10, Box 164)
  - Civil Liberties Alert, 1977-1981 (Folder 11, Box 164)
  - Civiletti guidelines, 1980-1981 (Folder 1, Box 165)
    FBI, Informants, Criminal Investigations
  - Civiletti guidelines, 1980-1981 (Folder 2, Box 165)
  - Civiletti, Ben R., 1978-1980 (Folder 3, Box 165)
  - Classification-[Ronald] Reagan executive order, 1983 (Folder 4, Box 165)
    Federal Employees, National Security Intelligence, Polygraph
  - Clinics - Abortion, 1984-1985 (Folder 5, Box 165)
    Bombings
  - Clinton [William Jefferson]-[Francisco Martin] Duran, 1994-1995 (Folder 6, Box 165)
  - CNSS-FOIA (Folder 7, Box 165)
    Center for National Security Studies, Freedom of Information Act
  - CNSS-Literature, 1976-1981 (Folder 8, Box 165)
  - CNSS-Literature, 1976-1981 (Folder 9, Box 165)
  - COHA-[Larry] Birns, 1977, 1989 (Folder 10, Box 165)
    Council on Hemispheric Affairs
  - Committee for National Security, 1980-1990 (Folder 11, Box 165)
    Militarism
  - Communist agent entry, 1976-1986 (Folder 1, Box 166)
    Visa Restrictions
  - Computer-security, 1980-1988 (Folder 2, Box 166)
  - Computer security and intelligence, 1980s (Folder 3, Box 166)
  - Congress-Korea, 1976-1977 (Folder 4, Box 166)
    Korea, Newspaper Clippings
  - Congress Letter - Frank R. Wolf, June 28, 1991 (Folder 5, Box 166)
  - Consortium for the Study of Intelligence, 1982 (Folder 6, Box 166)
  - Consortium for the Study of Intelligence, 1982 (Folder 7, Box 166)
  - Consortium for the Study of Intelligence, 1982 (Folder 8, Box 166)
  - Consortium for the Study of Intelligence, [Counterintelligence:] Requirements for the 1980s (Folder 9, Box 166)
  - Counterintelligence, 1978-1988 (Folder 10, Box 166)
  - Counterintelligence, 1980s (Folder 11, Box 166)
    Congressional Hearings, Department of Justice, Newspaper Clippings
  - Counterintelligence, 1980s (Folder 1, Box 167)
    Department of Justice, Newspaper Clippings, Notes
  - Counterintelligence-CIA, 1976-1988 (Folder 2, Box 167)
  - Counterspy II (post '76), 1978-1983 (Folder 3, Box 167)
    Anti-Intelligence, Congressional Records, Counterspy
  - Counterspy II (post '76), 1978-1983 (Folder 4, Box 167)
    Anti-Intelligence, Counterspy
  - Covert Action Information Bulletin, 1978-1981 (Folder 5, Box 167)
    Anti-Intelligence, CIA, Counterintelligence, FBI
  - Covert Action Information Bulletin, 1978-1981 (Folder 6, Box 167)
  - Coverage-CISPES, 1986-1989 (Folder 7, Box 167)
  - CPDS-([James L.]Tyson), 1977-1987 (Folder 8, Box 167)
    Center for Public Diplomacy Studies
  - CPR [Campaign for Political Rights], 1979-1982 (Folder 9, Box 167)
    Campaign for Political Rights
  - CPR-ON [Campaign for Political Rights-Organizing Notes], 1979-1982 (Folder 10, Box 167)
  - Criminal standard, 1980s (Folder 1, Box 168)
    Courts
  - Croats-Serbs, 1976-1987 (Folder 2, Box 168)
    Bosnia-Herzegovina, Yugoslavia
  - Crowther, Bosley, 1952 (Folder 3, Box 168)
    Film
  - CSI-NSIC-'81: Clandestine Collection, 1981 (Folder 4, Box 168)
    Consortium for the Study of Intelligence, National Strategy Information Center
  - CSI-NSIC-'81: Clandestine Collection, 1981 (Folder 5, Box 168)
  - CSP [folder 1 of 2], 1994 (Folder 6, Box 168)
    Center for Security Policy
  - CSP [folder 2 of 2], 1992-1994 (Folder 7, Box 168)
  - Cuba - Embargo: Propaganda and Reality, 1994 (Folder 8, Box 168)
    Cuba, Foreign Policy
  - Cuba-Soviet Troops, etc., 1979-1980 (Folder 9, Box 168)
    Cold War, Embargo
  - Daniloff, Nicholas, 1986 (Folder 10, Box 168)
  - Daniloff, Nicholas, 1986 (Folder 11, Box 168)
  - D. C. Latino Riot, 1991 (Folder 12, Box 168)
    Cuba, Newspaper Clippings, Riots, Washington, D.C.
  - Dell and FMLN-CISPES, ca. 1980 (Folder 13, Box 168)
  - Dellums, Ronald V., 1983-1988 (Folder 1, Box 169)
    Inside Washington, Newspaper Clippings
  - Dellums [Ronald V.]-general-intelligence, 1991-1992 (Folder 2, Box 169)
  - Dellums [Ronald V.]-Grenada, 1982-1991 (Folder 3, Box 169)
    Dellums, Foreign Policy, Grenada, Newspaper Clippings
  - Denton Bill (S. 2469), 1984 (Folder 4, Box 169)
  - Department of Justice, 1976-1980 (Folder 5, Box 169)
    Department of Justice, FBI Guidelines, Investigative Journalism
  - Disinformation, Winter, 1987 (Folder 6, Box 169)
    Foreign Policy, Soviet Union
  - Dissent Paper (El Salvador), 1981-1985 (Folder 7, Box 169)
    KGB, Forgery, El Salvador
  - Drug testing, 1985-1988 (Folder 8, Box 169)
    Drugs
  - Drug testing, 1985-1988 (Folder 9, Box 169)
  - Drug testing, 1977-1989 (Folder 10, Box 169)
  - Drug testing, 1977-1989 (Folder 11, Box 169)
  - Dupont plaza fire-San Juan, Puerto Rico, 1987 (Folder 12, Box 169)
    Puerto Rico
  - Edelmans - CHILDS DEF FND, 1994-1997 (Folder 13, Box 169)
    Children's Defense Fund
  - El Salvador, 1981 (Folder 14, Box 169)
    El Salvador, Reagan, Sandanistas
  - El Salvador Pre-1980, 1979-1978 (Folder 15, Box 169)
  - El Salvador, 1980 (Folder 1, Box 170)
  - El Salvador, 1981 (Folder 2, Box 170)
  - El Salvador, 1982 (Folder 3, Box 170)
  - El Salvador, 1983 (Folder 4, Box 170)
  - El Salvador, 1984 (Folder 5, Box 170)
  - El Salvador, 1985 (Folder 6, Box 170)
  - El Salvador, 1986 (Folder 7, Box 170)
  - El Salvador, 1987 (Folder 8, Box 170)
  - El Salvador, 1988 (Folder 9, Box 170)
  - El Salvador, 1989 (Folder 10, Box 170)
  - El Salvador, 1990 (Folder 11, Box 170)
  - El Salvador: Cessna Plane Crash, etc., 1989 (Folder 12, Box 170)
  - El Salvador-peace talks, 1988-1991 (Folder 13, Box 170)
    Marxist Rebels, Newspaper Clippings
  - El Salvador US policy, 1981-1990 (Folder 14, Box 170)
    Foreign Policy, Newspaper Clippings
  - El Salvador US policy, 1982-1990 (Folder 15, Box 170)
  - Enveloped Materials: DJ - Kearney, etc., 1976-1980 (Folder 1, Box 171)
    Committee on Foreign Affairs, Justice Department
  - Enveloped Materials: Civil Suits - Kearney (Folder 2, Box 171)
    Kearney, McNamara, Trial
  - Enveloped Materials: KEARNEY INDICT - TRIAL PROCEEDS, ETC., 1977-1978 (Folder 3, Box 171)
  - Enveloped Materials: Press on Indicts, 1980 (Folder 4, Box 171)
  - Enveloped Materials: Protests, 1977-1978 (Folder 5, Box 171)
    McNamara, Protests, Riots
  - Enveloped Materials: G-F-M "Trial", 1977-1980 (Folder 6, Box 171)
    Courts, Trial Transcripts
  - Enveloped Materials: C-Gov't, 1982 (Folder 7, Box 171)
    Heritage Foundation, McNamara
  - Enveloped Materials: Carter Policy and Quayle, 1989 (Folder 8, Box 171)
    McNamara, United States Global Strategy Council
  - Enveloped Materials: Elections, 1982-1989 (Folder 9, Box 171)
  - Enveloped Materials: Salv-U.S.S.R., 1980s (Folder 10, Box 171)
    El Salvador, Soviet Union
  - Enveloped Materials: FBI CISPES (folder 1 of 2), 1980s (Folder 11, Box 171)
    Committee in Solidarity with the People of El Salvador
  - Enveloped Materials: FBI CISPES (folder 2 of 2), 1980s (Folder 12, Box 171)